<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>rebekah_curse</name>
    <directory>rebekah_curse</directory>
    <id>2540075442</id>
    <description>[h1]Rebekah, Isaac's fated wife has stormed the basement![/h1]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/xDpL6ty.png[/img]

[b]Play as Rebekah, the quiet, roleplaying bookworm who used to stalk Isaac and write imaginative adventures and stories about him. [/b]

She is a pot filled with genuine love and a pinch of craze, nothing stops Rebekah in reaching Isaac to marry him.
However, she doesn't know what is Isaac's ideal girl!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/ziXgz5b.gif[/img]

Luckily for us, she had developed abilities with the power of love! Change her playstyle by picking her personalities based on the base game's Hearts!

Double tap to perform a special dash based on her personality!

Use her gun to perform a special barrage!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/T9rETLQ.png[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/MeiRzQT.gif[/img]

[h1][u]Changing personalities as Rebekah is easy.[/u][/h1]
After defeating the boss of any given floor, a mirror will spawn in the middle of the room, displaying all the heart types you currently hold. 

When you find the personality you want to change into, simply touch the mirror change Rebecca to that mode!

If you are far away from the mirror, it quickly shifts from one heart to the other.
You can also get close to the mirror, making the heart transitions slower. Just a useful tip just in case you are impatient!

[h1][u]If you want to get picky, blow up the mirror to get all kinds of hearts in the game! [/u][/h1]
This way, you can also have new ways to get new modes with this method!
However, you lose your ability to change a mode in that floor, so be wise!

On a new run, Rebekah can also randomly start with any heart type along with a red heart and an empty heart container.

This gives you an advantage in having randomized experiences with each personality, each time!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/qfhc5Ra.png[/img]

[/h1][b]Rebekah has no idea what kind of girl Isaac likes. Luckily for her, she knows all romantic archetypes based from books she read.[/b][/h1]
Her personalities allows her to change her look, abilities and playstyles! 

[img]https://i.imgur.com/xJTlgF0.gif[/img]

[b]Become the shy and introverted bookworm Red Heart, bright and aloof Soul Heart, sophisticated Gold Heart, mischieveous Evil Heart, 
mature and level-headed Eternal Heart, the dumb-wild Bone Heart, and even the Repentance exclusive modes like the hyper-active Rotten Heart or 
even the know-it-all Broken Heart.[/b]

[i]But remember, these are not all for show, these all change your gameplay, so pick your favorites![/i]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/rkaI8Tr.png[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/8HFUD3n.gif[/img]

[h1][b] Her new pocket item, Hugs and Roses, allows you to shoot a powerful special action that will benefit you and your playstyle.[/b] [/h1]

You use special charges from your new special heart reserve bar right under your health hud. 

If empty, simply use your pocket item to refill your bar with a cost of half a heart or kill enough enemies to refill it.
If you have no red hearts, further attempts of refilling will break your health bar, giving broken hearts.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pIzhTLO.gif[/img]

When you have up to 12 broken hearts, you immediately die. Don't break Rebekah's heart!


[img]https://i.imgur.com/H5u04JR.png[/img]
[list]
[h1]Why does Rebekah look like Maggy?[/h1]
  [*]The mod must be bugged. Make sure you have SchoolbagAPI subscribed or unsubscribe to this mod and resubscribe for reinstallation.

[h1]What happened to the unlocks?[/h1]
  [*]The mod was too big to port and polish into Repentance so the items will come in a later date as a separate update.

[h1]Where is the Tainted Rebekah?/I tried to play Tainted Rebekah but I just turn back into regular Rebekah[/h1]
  [*]She doesn't exist. Yet. She will come in a later update.

[h1]What happened to Red Heart's 20/20?[/h1]
  [*]Repentance broke that feature, we have to wait until they fix that. Sorry for the inconvenience!

[h1]I found a bug![/h1]
  [*]Bugs go here: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2540075442/3044979493853537391/]  link  [/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/EZcylt3.png![/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/4VJsI8O.png[/img]

[list]
  [*]KakaoDCat - the majority of the mod code, sprites and voices for the gold knights.
  [*]JudeInutil - porting this mod and polsihed the sprites into Repentance
  [*]lambchop - helped with the development of AB+ Rebekah
  [*]yatboim - cleaned up the AB+ code, reworked the awesome double tap system
  [*]ItsnotArthor - artist for the thumbnail
  [*]meg - did the crazy cute voice for Rebekah. 
[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z9QmXxo.png[/img]

[list]
  [*]AgentCucco/_Kilburn -the GetPlayerBlackHearts system Kilburn made for Cucco's Soul Heart Rebalance mod. 
  [*]tem -the Strawman system and the custom Eden hair system which Rebekah now uses
  [*]Sentinel - helped with many issues in the past
  [*]Sanio - helped with the mega mush costume system
  [*]Dumpy - helped with the CanShoot system
[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/aCaq76J.png[/img]

[list]
  [*]Cube-erry Cherry
  [*]TheMemeingOfIsaac/Ysak
  [*]Abyss Knight/Baraka
  [*]Apostle
  [*]Zanariff/Zana
[/list]


[h1]-Special Thanks-[/h1]
Sites like SoundBible, FreeSound, zapsplat and soundsnap - some sounds I couldn't get by myself. This isn't commercialized!
[h1][b]And the community - for your support and love for this mod! Thank you for waiting so long for this Repentance port! I hope you stay tuned for the Tainted and Items update![/b][/h1]</description>
    <version>1.3</version>
    <visibility>Private</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
</metadata>
