<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>rebekah_curse</name>
    <directory>rebekah_curse</directory>
    <id>2540075442</id>
    <description>[b]Prerequisites for the best experience[/b]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/cMdILeT.png[/img]
[h1]Rebekah, Isaac's fated wife has stormed the basement![/h1]

[b]Rebekah, the Cursed and Brokenhearted Expansion[/b]

This expansion adds Rebekah,the quiet, roleplaying magical girl, secret and future wife of Isaac, 50+ new items and trinkets, one new consumable, one new room type, one new boss and much more! 

More content like more enemies and maybe even floors might come soon! Keep an eye of this mod while you're at it, no promises!

https://i.imgur.com/mY5LMGl.png

[img]https://i.imgur.com/xDpL6ty.png[/img]

She is a pot filled with genuine love and a pinch of craze, nothing stops Rebekah in reaching Isaac to marry him.
However, she doesn't know what is Isaac's ideal girl!

Luckily for us, she had developed abilities with the power of magical girl love! Change her playstyle by picking her personalities based on the base game's Hearts!

Double tap to perform a special dash based on her personality!

Use her gun to perform a special barrage! Usable only if you have enough love-love meter. To have meter, kill enough enemies!

[img]https://imgur.com/Jcnvtq4.gif[/img]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/nPLDJuv.png[/img]

[h1][b] Her new pocket items, a magical girl gun allows you to shoot a powerful special action that will benefit you and your playstyle.[/b] [/h1]

You use special charges from your new special heart reserve bar right under your health hud. 

If empty, simply use your pocket item to refill your bar with a cost of half a heart or kill enough enemies to refill it.
If you have no red hearts, further attempts of refilling will break your health bar, giving broken hearts.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pIzhTLO.gif[/img]

When you have up to 12 broken hearts, you immediately die. Don't break Rebekah's heart!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/MeiRzQT.gif[/img]

[h1][u]Changing personalities as Rebekah is easy.[/u][/h1]
If you want to change personalities mid-game, it's easy!

After defeating the boss of any given floor, a mirror will spawn in the middle of the room, displaying all the heart types you currently hold. 

When you find the personality you want to change into, simply touch the mirror change Rebecca to that mode!

[img]https://i.imgur.com/xJTlgF0.gif[/img]

For a wiki for more info, go here in this wiki! One day we will also have Encyclopedia support but not now:
 [url=https://rebekah-the-cursed-and-the-heartbroken.fandom.com/wiki/Rebekah] WIKI [/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/H5u04JR.png[/img]
[list]
[h1]Why does Rebekah look like Maggy?[/h1]
  [*]The mod must be bugged. Make sure you have InutilLib subscribed or unsubscribe to this mod and resubscribe for reinstallation.

[h1]What happened to the unlocks?[/h1]
  [*]The mod is still focusing on other things, but unlocks are coming soon-ish now!

[h1]Where is the Tainted Rebekah?/I tried to play Tainted Rebekah but I just turn back into regular Rebekah[/h1]
  [*]She doesn't exist. Yet. She will come in a later update.

[h1]I found a bug![/h1]
  [*]Bugs go here: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2540075442/3044979493853537391/]  link  [/url]

[h1]Do you have a discord server?[/h1]
  [*]Yes we do! Here, you can beta test for the upcoming updates or just hang out with others who like this expansion, right [url=https://discord.gg/K5qEUFsFch] here! [/url] You can also report a bug in here if you want me to see it quickly.

[h1]This is disgusting. Isaac is five![/h1]
  [*]Rebekah is also five.
  [*]Rebekah is a child who says stuff they don't mean. Marriage is one of them. Look at Panini in Chowder.
  [*]Rebekah is the canon wife of Isaac in the Bible.
  [*]Even if none of the things above is true, nothing sexual is happening, you weirdos. Go to church.

[h1]*insert something 177013 related something[/h1]
  [*]Yes. It was based of this back then because I wanted to traumatize people. That's all.


[img]https://i.imgur.com/EZcylt3.png![/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/6VQ8ZlP.png[/img]

[list]
  [*]KakaoDCat - the majority of the mod code, sprites and voices for the gold knights.
  [*]JudeInutil - porting this mod and polsihed the sprites into Repentance
  [*]Scorch71 - coder who wanted to help!
  [*]lambchop - helped with the development of AB+ Rebekah
  [*]yatboim - cleaned up the AB+ code, reworked the awesome double tap system
  [*]ItsnotArthor - artist for the thumbnail
  [*]meg - did the crazy cute voice for Rebekah. 
  [*]Mayonez - awesome musician
  [*]Sabra - wiki manager
  [*]Frithian - Public Relations guy!
  [*]zero- first spriter, been here for so long, really cool!
  [*]Goncholito - former spriter
  [*]imPupzables - spriter with a dead dog
  [*]Scroto - spriter with epic powers
  [*]Aladar - former spriter penguin
  [*]Susuke - former spriter who did something!
  [*]Kruntical - former spriter who IS sus
[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z9QmXxo.png[/img]

[list]
  [*]AgentCucco/_Kilburn -the GetPlayerBlackHearts system Kilburn made for Cucco's Soul Heart Rebalance mod. 
  [*]tem -the Strawman system and the custom Eden hair system which Rebekah now uses
  [*]Sentinel - helped with many issues in the past
  [*]Sanio - helped with the mega mush costume system
  [*]Dumpy - helped with the CanShoot system
  [*]Warhamm2000 - helped with the new code for mega mush sprites
  [*]Deadinfinity - stageapi help
  [*]Planetarium Chance - for using their code to render the Love Room percentage stats
[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/2pfVC5n.png[/img]

[list]
  [*]Cube-erry Cherry
  [*]TheMemeingOfIsaac/Ysak
  [*]Abyss Knight/Baraka
  [*]Apostle
  [*]Zanariff/Zana
  [*]Mars
  [*]Kaethela
  [*]Masquerade
  [*]Collided
  [*]Shadeshadow227
  [*]Duo
  [*]Mr. L
  [*]Skyline222
  [*]Shuckster
[/list]


[h1]-Special Thanks-[/h1]
Sites like SoundBible, FreeSound, zapsplat and soundsnap - some sounds I couldn't get by myself. This isn't commercialized!
[h1][b]And the community - for your support and love for this mod! Thank you for waiting so long for this Repentance port! I hope you stay tuned for the Tainted and Items update![/b][/h1]</description>
    <version>1.36</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Items"/>
    <tag id="Active Items"/>
    <tag id="Pills"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
    <tag id="Familiars"/>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Bosses"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
    <tag id="Graphics"/>
    <tag id="Music"/>
</metadata>
